Never could imagine there were only
Tending the ways to love somebody
Lalalalalalala
Can't you see?
I'm like your feet
Whenever, forever
We need to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near
And that's the deal, my dear
They're all what you wonder
You never have to wonder
We can always play by ear
But that's the deal, my dear
Lalalalalalala
Lucky for my mits, not only mumble
Cause real kisses like a thumb
Lucky for my presters, more than humble
So you don't confuse them with smiles
Lucky I have strong words like my momma
To love a cover when I need it
I face to rise up for no other
The day we will cry over
Lalalalalalala
I'm like your feet
Whenever, forever
We need to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near
And that's the deal, my dear
They're all what you wonder
You never have to wonder
We can always play by ear
But that's the deal, my dear
Lalalalalalala
Think of that
Say it again
Lalalalalalala
Tell me one more time
Manually
Lost in my eyes
Whenever, forever
We need to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near
And that's the deal, my dear
They're all what you wonder
You've got me head over heels
There's nothing left to fear
If you really feel the way I feel
Whenever, forever
We need to be together
I'll be there and you'll be near
And that's the deal, my dear
They're all what you wonder
You've got me head over heels
There's nothing left to fear
If you really feel the way I feel